[✨Get 20% Off imagiCharms through Dec 23✨ - Last day for guaranteed delivery by Dec 25 has passed.](https://imagilabs.com/discount/codingjoy24?redirect=%2Fcollections%2Fshop-collection)

### Search our store

Popular Searches:

T-Shirt Blue Jacket

""

Privacy Policy
==============

[Home](https://imagilabs.com/ "Back to the home page") Privacy Policy

In short (and plain English), we are good people. We will never use your private information in a harmful way and never email you without your consent. We also dislike sites and companies that do that, and we respect your privacy, and clean inboxes!  
Below is the detailed privacy policy that based on our googling, we believe we must include.  
  
**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
**2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**  
**3\. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
**4\. HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION**  
**5\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US WITH PRIVACY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**  
  
Welcome to imagiLabs (“imagiLabs”, “we”, “us” or “our”). imagiLabs teaches you how to code and provides you with the ability to share your coding creations with others.  
  
Our Privacy Policy explains how we use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile application.  
  
By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to create and post content, including comments and other materials ("User Content"), to the Service and to share User Content publicly. This means that other Users may search for, see, use, or share any of your User Content that you make publicly available through the Service, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  
  
Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service ("Users").

### 1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect the following types of information:  

* Information you provide us directly:
* Your username, password and email address or phone number when you register for an imagiLabs account.
* Profile information that you provide for your user profile (e.g. bio, age). This information allows us to help you or others be "found" on imagiLabs.
* User Content (e.g., coding projects and comments) that you create and post in the Service.
* Communications between you and imagiLabs. For example, we may send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). Note that you may not opt out of Service-related emails.

**Analytics information:**

* We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

### 2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive to:

* help you efficiently access your information after you sign in
* remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Service;
* provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or other forms of marketing
* provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service
* develop and test new products and features
* monitor metrics such as total number of users, traffic, and demographic patterns
* diagnose or fix technology problems
* automatically update the imagiLabs application on your device

### 3\. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside imagiLabs without your consent, except in the event of a change of control or in response to a legal request.  
  
If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of imagiLabs or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as name and email address, User Content and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.  
  
We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. We may also access, preserve and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to: detect, prevent and address fraud and other illegal activity; to protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of investigations; and to prevent death or imminent bodily harm. Information we receive about you may be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.

### 4\. HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION

* Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in Sweden or any other country in which imagiLabs, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities.
* imagiLabs, its Affiliates, or Service Providers may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
* By registering for and using the Service you consent to the transfer of information to Sweden or to any other country in which imagiLabs, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
* We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through the Service secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. However, imagiLabs cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to imagiLabs or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.
* Please do your part to help us. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to emails between you and imagiLabs, at all times.

### 5\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US WITH PRIVACY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

We are happy to answer any questions you might have concerning your personal Data, third-party processors or in-app safety. For general questions, please contact us at [support@imagilabs.com](mailto:support@imagilabs.com "support@imagilabs.com").

### For Educators

### For Parents

### Products

### Our Team

### Media

### More

* * *

**imagiLabs AB**

Medborgarplatsen 25, 118 72

Stockholm, Sweden

©2023 imagiLabs AB. All Rights Reserved.
